this is a National
Emergency Detonator
charged we're in the race against
and I know what it and I know what it means
if the Nazis have a
bomb we 12mon head start 18 how could you possibly
know that we've got one hope all America's industrial might
and hope all America's industrial might and scientific innovation connected
here secret
laboratory keep everyone there until laboratory keep everyone there until it's
done
let's go recruit some
scientists build a town it fast we don't let scientist
bring their families don't let scientist bring their families will'll
never get the best why would we go to the
middle of nowhere for who knows how
nowhere for who knows how long why
about because this is the most important thing that ever
the most important thing that ever happened in the history
of
happened in the history of world you're the great improviser
but
this you can't do in your you can't do in your head
are we saying there's a chance that when we push
button destroy the we world chances are near zero
what do you want from Theory alone zero would be
nice this is a matter of life and death but
I can perform this death but I can perform this miracle
War II would be over our boys would come
home that's happening isn't
it the world will remember this
day our work here will ensure a peace mankind has
never
seen until somebody builds a bigger one
you are the man who gave them the power to
destroy themselves and the world is not
5 4 3 Truman needs to know what's next two
one